# **ASAHI YAMAMOTO**

C++ & WEB DEVELOPER

Phone Number: +41-44-586-3155

email: asahi.yamamoto0125@gmail.com

Address: Japan, Matsura-shi

### **ABOUT ME**

Enthusiastic and creative Web | C++ | MFC Developer with diverse knowledge in this field. I like to build amazing and interesting things that matter. Have years of hands-on experience efficiently coding websites and mobile applications using modern JavaScript, Typescript, Python, PHP, Ruby frameworks, and beautiful UI frameworks. Over the last 6 months, I mainly focused on Blockchain technologies - developing Front-end with Web3 / ether.js/Polka dot/Solidity, Token and Coin development.

I like to learn new things and I am looking forward to working an exciting and challenging projects. I am continuously trying to improve, learn more and gain new experiences.

With a strong attention to detail and accuracy and the important ability to function well in a team working.

# **EDUCATION**

### Tokyo Institute of Technology

Master of Computer Applications (M.C.A.) • Shinjuku City, Tokyo 04/2014 I've got a deep knowledge of the program language & DevOps while going to this university.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### SENIOR Full Stack DEVELOPER

Care Of (via Angel) 2019.05-2022.06

- Developed a Quora-like site using React, React Hooks front end with GraphQL for a home-care service company based in Australia.
- Implemented mobile-responsive front-end pages with React, Bootstrap, and SCSS.
- Used Apollo-boost to consume GraphQL API.
- Engaged back-end development in Nest.js and PostgreSQL.

Technologies: GraphQL, PostgreSQL, Node.js, SCSS, Bootstrap, NestJS, Boost, Apollo, React

#### Full-stack JavaScript Expert

Roubler Pte Ltd (via Angel) 2018.09-2019.04

- Developed Basic JavaScript applications for client projects
- Converted and upgraded existing client accounts and upsold to existing clients for new digital services
- Conducted A/B Testing to identify bugs and UI improvements

#### React, Node.js Developer

TRM Labs (via Toptal)

- 2017.10-2018.08
- Joined the team as a React and Node.js developer with cryptocurrency experience.
- Implemented React High-Order-Components along with Antd.
- Implemented REST APIs with FeathersJS.
- Wrote Blockchain-related helper functions.

#### C++ & MFC DEVELOPER

TRM Labs (via Toptal) 2014.05-2022.06

Developed various projects, many communication programs, testing and checking programs, etc.

# **SKILLS**

TS, Python, Solidity, C, C#, Rust, Golang, Ruby, Node.js, React, Vue, Next, Nuxt, Angular, Laravel, Django, Flask, Heroku, React Native, BootStrap, GraphQL, Api Integration, HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, Ethereum, Truffle, Web3js, Polka dot

# **LANGUAGE**

English Chinese